

Jose Julio De Júlio de Sant'Ana Sant Ana Angeli

Brazil

Education

Technologist in Computing -Business Management emphasis, FATEC, BR, 2012

Languages

English - Good

Portuguese - Fluent

Spanish - Basic

Profile

Worked as electronics technician until 2009, when gone back to study. Faculty ended in june 2012.

Joined to IBM in 2011, through the BTP program, as SAP-ABAP programmer. In March 2012 achieve to be transferred to DBA competence. Working as Microsoft SQL-Server DBA.

Key skills

Java SE Programmer (Jr) - IBM Academic Certified DB2 Fundamentals - SQL-Server DBA.

Hadoop Foundations Level 2 badge: https://yourlearning.ibm.com/#badge/A_3e335dbc-0f7f-44d0-9809-10cfb26eb05f

Key courses and training

Object Oriented Programming. Java Programmer. DB2 9.7 Fundamentals PL/SQL (IBM).
Unix fundamentals (IBM)
Hadoop Fundamentals (Badge - Acclaim)
Microsoft AZ-900 Certification exam: Azure F

Microsoft AZ-900 Certification exam: Azure Fundamentals.

Microsoft DP-900 Certification exam. Azure Data Fundamentals.

Git e GitHub - Essencial para o desenvolvedor - Udemy

Work experience

IT Specialist

IBM, Brazil | Mar 2012 - Present

DBA - SQL-Server

SAP-ABAP Consultant (Jr)

IBM, Brazil | Nov 2011 - Mar 2012

SAP-ABAP Developer.

SAP-ABAP (Trainee BTP)

IBM, Brazil | Aug 2011 - Nov 2011



Learn SAP-ABAP language.

Single Worker

Sigle Worker, Brazil | Jan 1997 - Jul 2011

Receiving and fixing eletronics from clients. Making all necessary for acomplish client's needs.

Assignment history

SQL Server DBA

North American Telecomunications company., Brazil | Mar 2012 - Present

Telecommunications industry database maintenance.

Contribution: Microsoft SQL-Server DBA.

Ensure databases Health and Availability, as well as security and recovery in the case of a problem in the system.

Primary DBA of two systems, one called FLUX and other REVEAL. FLUX and REVEAL are data warehouse systems charged to hold data from the RF systems that Sprint provides to clients.

FLUX and REVEAL were decommissioned and now it is moved to PRTS-RAN for FLUX and PRTS-PCMD for REVEAL. I am still primary DBA for both.

Additional information

Performed missioner role from 1997 to 2007 in Montes Claros - MG, Brazil.